

Mihail Divjakoski

Date of birth: 16/11/1998

Nationality: Macedonian/citizen of the Republic of North Macedonia

Gender: Male | **Phone number:** (+389) 75752756 (Mobile) | **Email address:**

divjakoski.mihail@gmail.com Website:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mihail-divjakoski-613697154? fbclid=lwAR30uOmLUF7hvtrzHb8rDQbQVG6JT05y_6Ghi6ahXrCJD4L4dbrk-CuVIAU

Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100017748247755

Whatsapp Messenger: +38975752756

Address: Village Krusheani, st. Arhiepiskop Dositej no.42, 7524, Municipality of Krivogashtani, North Macedonia (Home)

About me:

Eager for new challenges and experiences, highly creative individual with proven organizational skills within and outside of a workplace. Detail-oriented, always a people person and a hard-working individual. Strong analytical and research skills with a track record of achieving positive outcomes for clients.

WORK EXPERIENCE

22/02/2021 - CURRENT Bitola, North Macedonia

MEDICAL BILLER- ACCOUNTS RECEIVABLE SPECIALIST TASKFORCE BPO

Detail oriented Medical Billing Specialist with two years of experience handling billing and clerical tasks, ensuring accurate and Timely claims billing. Proven track record in dealing with complicated accounts and claims.

- In charge of working an average of 50 to 70 claims a day up to resolution.
- Close communication with clients and third-party insurance companies/patients.
- Following up on submitted claims/appeals.
- Training over 30 new employees over the course of the past two years via shadowing process.
- Stepping up in short-term leading/managing roles when needed.
- Meeting up tight deadlines, including sometimes working overtime.
- Working under pressure/ managing stressful situations

Business or Sector Financial and insurance activities

Department Medical Billing, RCM (Revenue-cycle management)

Address Aron Aroesti br. 1, 7000, Bitola, North Macedonia | Email contact@taskforcebpo.com |

Website https://taskforcebpo.com/

01/09/2019 – 20/12/2020 Prilep, Krushevo, Municipality of Krivogashtani, Municipality of Dolneni, North Macedonia **MARKET RESEARCH INTERVIEWER** IPSOS- MACEDONIA

Inventory on drinks in all selling subjects in the named four municipalities, analyzing data, data management

Business or Sector Other service activities | **Department** Market Research |

Address st. Kairska 31, 1000, Skopje, North Macedonia | Email office.macedonia@ipsos.com

Website https://www.ipsos.com/mk-mk

01/02/2018 - 15/03/2019 Prilep, North Macedonia

PART-TIME JOB, COMMERCIAL AGENT GRAWE INSURANCE

Direct meeting with potential clients, presenting our services and selling **Business or Sector** Financial and insurance activities | **Department** Life insurance |

Address st. Pirinska, no.23, 1000, Skopje, North Macedonia | Email office.skopje@grawe.at

Website https://www.grawe.mk/

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/10/2017 - 29/09/2022 Prilep, North Macedonia

BARCHELOR STUDIES Faculty of Economics- Prilep

Address st. Marksova 133, Prilep, North Macedonia | Website http://eccfp.edu.mk/

27/02/2020 - 15/07/2020 Split, Croatia

ERASMUS STUDIES SCHOLARSHIP Faculty of Economics- Split, Sveuciliste u Splitu- UNIST

Marketing Communications Marketing Strategies Financial Management Entrepreneurial Planning

Address Cvite Fiskovica 5, Split, Croatia | Website http://www.efst.unist.hr/ |

Field of study Marketing and advertising | Final grade 3.5 | Type of credits ECTS | Number of credits 20

01/09/2013 - 15/06/2017 Prilep, North Macedonia

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA SOEPTU "Kuzman Josifoski- Pitu"

Bank working

Bank calculations and operations

Business communication

Address st. Car samoil 1A, Prilep, North Macedonia | **Website** http://kjpitu.edu.mk/

Field of study Finance, banking and insurance | Final grade 3.5

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): MACEDONIAN

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
CROATIAN	C1	B1	B2	B2	B2
ENGLISH	C1	B2	C1	C1	C1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

Google | Canva | Google suite (Gmail Google Drive Google Slide Google Docs Google Sheets Google Forms Google) | Social Media | Video Conferencing (Zoom Skype Google Hangout)

Soft Skills

Organizational and planning skills | Decision-making | Team-work oriented | Motivated | Responsibi lity | Critical thinking | Creativity | Good listener and communicator | Presenting | Reliability | Writte n and Verbal skills | Conflict resolution | Microsoft Office

DRIVING LICENCE

Driving Licence: B

CONFERENCES AND SEMINARS

16/03/2021 - 23/04/2021 - Online Event

HR STARTER 2021 An intensive HR training program organized by HR World, supported by the HR Association in North Macedonia. Organized within the course of six weeks, covering the topics of:

- · HR as a strategic function
- Employee Development
- HR and Transformation
- Recruitment and Selection
- People Analytics & HR Tech
- Future of HR

This program was consisted of both theoretical and practical parts, where us, the participants, had the opportunity to learn through practice by organizing interviews as being both the interviewer and the candidate. Happy to have been a part of such an amazing and fulfilling experience. Gained certificate of completion on the whole program with over 90% participation.

16/11/2020 - 20/11/2020 - Online Event

SMecoMP educational training

Link https://www.facebook.com/SMecoMP

05/11/2020 - 10/11/2020 - Online Event

International Youth Conference- Krushevo

Link https://www.facebook.com/YouthConferenceKrusevo

09/12/2019 - 13/12/2019 - Novi Sad, Serbia

Capacity Building Training Course "Western Balkans Capacity Building" - Young European Federalists- JEF Europe

17/09/2019 - 23/09/2019 - Istanbul, Turkey

ERASMUS+ Contact Making seminar "Drop Effect: Creating Sustainability in Youth Projects"

13/06/2019 - 16/06/2019 - Struga, North Macedonia

National conference- Structural dialogue "Youth Work in prevention of violent Extremism"-Coalition SEGA

15/04/2019 - 15/04/2019

Macedonia Model United Nations- MMUN 2019- Coalition SEGA

03/04/2019 - 11/04/2019

ERASMUS+ Training Course "Empowerment through (social) Entrepreneurship- Fondacija Dobry Rozwój

11/03/2019 - 15/03/2019 - Molfetta, Italy

ERASMUS+ Workshop Seminar "A workshop in a Sustainable Society" - Associazione InCo - Interculturalità & Comunicazione

02/02/2019 - 09/09/2019

ERASMUS+ Training Course "Training course for organizers and facilitators "Road to the future"-Young European Federalists- JEF Europe

21/12/2018 - 22/12/2018 - Prilep, North Macedonia

Seminar "Manage to Succeed" - AIESEC LC Prilep

18/11/2018 - 26/11/2018 - Vinkovci, Croatia

ERASMUS+ Youth Exchange "Rule the world- Become an Entrepreneur"- Udruga Kor

04/10/2018 - 10/10/2018 - Cortemilia, Italy

ERASMUS+ Youth Exchange "Socemployable"- SFERA International; Agenzia Nazionale Per i Giovani

08/03/2018 - 11/03/2018 - Ohrid, North Macedonia

Conference "Balkan Cooperation Congress"- AIESEC Macedonia

01/12/2017 - 08/12/2017 - Osijek, Croatia

ERASMUS+ Youth Exchange "We Come As One"- INTERaktiva

20/11/2017 - 25/11/2017 - Trakai, Lithuania

ERASMUS+ Youth Exchange "Social Advertising for Peace"- Association Baltic Turkish Culture Academy

08/02/2017 - 09/02/2017 - Skopje, North Macedonia

Debate conference "Integrated Talks" - Youth Educational Forum / Младински Образовен Форум

10/12/2016 - 14/12/2016 - Prilep, North Macedonia

"Now a refugee- Always a human" - UNHCR- the UN Refugee Agency

13/10/2016 - 15/10/2016 - Skopje, North Macedonia

Debate Academy "IIEP Debate Academy"- USAID; Youth Educational forum / Младински образовен Форум

RECOMMENDATIONS

Jasna Dimovska Senior Team Lead

To whom it may concern,

Recommendation Letter for Mr. Mihail Divjakoski

I would like to recommend Mihail Divjakoski for any and all plans and intentions for the future, whether that be a job position application, postgraduate studies, institution or various other engagements.

He has been a member of my Team for the past year and a half. As his team leader I have witnessed incredible growth both as an employee and team member and as a person.

As someone who has been in the position of a team leader of a large team of over 110 people working on two clients, I have been able to recognize when there is great potential in my team members, one of them being Mihail.

Email jasna.dimovska@taskforcebpo.com | Phone (+389) 75592449

PROJECTS

15/09/2020 - 25/12/2020

"Environmental management and eco-entrepreneurship" - Interreg; Balkan- Mediterranean SMecoMP, University "st. Kliment Ohridski- Bitola"

01/11/2019 - 25/07/2020

"Град- Пријател на младите" / Youth Friendly City - Youth Alliance- Krushevo

14/07/2018 - 20/09/2018

"Advocating for local NGOs for active youth participation"- Preda PLUS; Coalition SEGA; Arbeiter-Samariter- Bund Edcuational trainings for the participants in Struga, North Macedonia, organizing series of workshops with youth from all the villages in the Municipality of Krivogashtani, creating Position Papers with problems, solutions and needs of the young people in the municipality, and then transfering the decument to the policy-makers in the municipality

10/06/2018 - 25/12/2018

"If stories could walk- If cities could talk" - Nasa djeca Zenica Series of educational meetings for all participants from three municipalities: Pancevo- Serbia, Zenica- Bosnia and Herzegovina; Prilep- North Macedonia.

Creating voice podcasts about important places in the three mentioned municipalities, and created audio map for the same three municipalities

01/10/2017 - 31/03/2018

EVS Project "Pulse Radio 2.0"- Youth Council- Prilep

15/06/2017 - 20/07/2017

Summer School for Entrepreneurship- youth Council- Prilep; Coalition SEGA

11/04/2016 - 10/09/2016

Summer School "YES- Young Entrepreneurial Start" - AIESEC LC Prilep

VOLUNTEERING

05/02/2018 - 26/12/2018 Council of Youth- Municipality of Krivogashtani

Founder/Member

20/06/2019 - 30/09/2020 Faculty Student Assembly- Faculty of Economics- Prilep

President Organizing events for students, fighting for student's rights, representation of students' voice in the policy-making bodies of the faculty

01/10/2020 - 30/09/2021 University Student Assembly- University "st.Kliment Ohridski"- Bitola

Member/ Finance Coordinator

20/11/2013 - 10/09/2020 Leo Club Prilep

Founder/Volunteer

05/03/2015 - 31/05/2020 Youth Council- Prilep

Volunteer Mentoring EVS/ESC volunteers, organizing different activities within the program of the organization, attending all kinds of events, volunteering in the internet radio "Pulse"

10/02/2019 - 05/10/2020 Local Action Group- LAG Agro Lider- Prilep

Volunteer

03/01/2018 – 20/09/2019 Youth Educational Forum/ Младински Образовен Форум YEf/MOФ- Debate club **Volunteer**

20/07/2017 - 05/03/2019 AIESEC Macedonia- LC Prilep

Member